[dramatic music]
Ha! This isn't real, right?
This is a prank!
[Nya] I'm sorry, but
I really don't think--
The dragon masters
are too powerful
to have been turned to stone.
I pulled this once.
Remember, Kai?
Wyldfyre
Time to wake them
from their slumber.
Ooh!
I'm gonna
Goochee-goochee-goo!
[laughs]
Egalt totally hates this,
don'tcha?
Goocheegoocheegooo?
Okay, plan B.
Ow!
All right.
Stone. Bad idea.
[sighs] Okay, so
it's not a prank,
but it'll wear off, right?
Right?
-I'm not sure.
-Lloyd?
I don't know. And we don't
have time to find out.
The Blood Moon's already rising,
which means Ras
can start the ritual
to free the Forbidden Five,
which will unleash evil on our
world like we've never known.
[Arin] But-- but that'll
never happen.
Kai, you've mastered
Rising Dragon technique.
All we gotta do is--
I haven't mastered
Rising Dragon.
Look, I did it once.
We could practice it more.
Then you could teach us.
But that's just it.
I don't know how I did it.
Not exactly.
It's the only fighting style
that can defeat Shatterspin.
Is there any other way
to stop Ras's ritual?
There's gotta be something.
No, not now! I can't handle
more visions! [yells]
[Cole] The Wyldness!
-Help! Help!
-[ominous music]
[gong rings]
[Lloyd gasping]
Lloyd! Are you okay?
More visions. I still can't
control when they come.
But I think I know
where we have to go.
Ras is going to perform
his ritual in the Wyldness.
We may not be ready,
but we don't have a choice.
It's time to face Ras,
or everything will be lost.
♪ Lost in the unknown,
so much to see ♪
♪ Together we will rise ♪
♪ We fight ♪
♪ Be a Ninja for what's right ♪
-[explosion booming]
-[dramatic music]
[guns blasting]
Get him!
File this permit in triplicate!
Really?
What? There aren't that many
places I can use that joke.
Focus on deactivating
the equipment known as Zane.
That is really quite rude.
Could equipment do this?
[shurikens clanking]
I mean, depending on its
programming, but point taken.
[guns blasting]
Ya!
Ha, and that old biddy Janet
said my crystal ball
didn't work right.
[crystal ball zapping]
[body thudding]
What does she know?
Works great.
[crystal ball beeping]
-Well, mostly.
-[whimsical music]
-[gas whizzes]
-Oh, ah! The onion!
Oh, my eyes are watering!
Oh, the stench burns!
Oh, it burns!
[guns blasting]
[crystal ball zapping]
[dramatic music]
Come at me!
I did ask for that.
Surrender the equipment now,
or we will charge you
with an additional violation.
Statute 27a, subparagraph 9.
That statute is just a fine.
You've already ordered
all of us terminated.
Right. Fair point.
Guess fines aren't
really an issue
if you're no longer alive.
My bad.
[metal clanking]
[guns blasting]
[crystal ball chimes]
[coconuts thudding]
Wow, coconuts. That's a first.
[guns blasting]
Come on! We've got to keep
them away from Bonzle!
[crystal ball zapping]
I said,
by the all-encompassing
authority of the Administration,
I hereby demand your surrender.
Um no
thank you.
[sighs] You're an accomplice
of the equipment
called Zane, right?
Rules say I have
to put you under arrest.
You could put me
under arrest, sure,
but I get the sense your
heart's not really in it.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Seems a little silly to me.
Ah, this job is really
rulesy, you know?
I don't remember
what I used to do
before the Administration,
but this is not the coolest
career or anything. [chuckles]
Oh, well, I'm supposed
to capture you,
so can you just let me do that?
Don't make it weird, hmm?
[dramatic music]
Hey! Get outta here, nightlight!
Ah! Knock it off!
[bright music]
What the
-Whoa!
-[electricity crackling]
How did you know I can do that?
No one knows I can
control lightning,
and no one can find out.
[dramatic music]
Ah!
Get away! You're
making this so weird!
[Jiro roars]
We'll get you in
a minute, buddy.
-[dramatic music]
-[metal thudding]
This is so easy.
It almost seems unfair.
[buttons beeping]
I quipped too soon.
[dramatic music continues]
[ice crackling]
That's one down!
[metal thuds]
[sword clanks]
That's two!
[crystal ball zapping]
Three, four, five!
I'm crushing it!
[dramatic music continues]
Are you properly
licensed to drive?
-[ice crunches]
-[dramatic music continues]
[guns blasting]
Keep them away while I
hack into their system.
Wouldn't kill you
to say please, but sure.
[crystal ball zapping]
I just need a bit more time
so I can set them
all to self-destruct.
[Cole] You got it!
Connecting to the system.
[guns blasting]
-[metal clanks]
-[electricity crackling]
[Zane] Data breach is failing!
Can't connect! Error!
Powering down.
Zane.
[dramatic music]
Zane! [grunts]
Talk to me, buddy.
[metal clanks]
[Cole shouts]
Are you okay in there?
[gun blasts]
I think his circuits got fried.
He just needs a little reboot.
What's the magic word?
Uh
Please?
Finally!
[crystal ball zapping]
[mech whirring]
-Huh?
-Zane! Are you okay?
[Zane] Confirmed.
All systems are stabilized.
And decoding is reactivating.
[computer beeping]
Data breach completed.
Hack attack!
[metal clanking]
[alert beeping]
Oh, this is gonna
be a lotta paperwork.
[agents screaming]
That can't be great.
[screams]
[agent groaning]
Hurry, no matter
how difficult it is,
we can't give up until
we find Bonzle, and--
-I found you!
-I found her.
That went more smoothly
than anticipated.
[dramatic music]
The magical storehouse is near.
So what now?
You're just gonna stuff
me in a storage box
till the Blood Moon passes?
Exactly.
Oh. I was kidding.
Magical Containment units
are incredibly safe.
Small, but safe. You're not
claustrophobic, are you?
If so, this would be
a really bad time to find out.
Oh, no. Look up ahead.
[Cole] The Cloud Kingdom!
Are they following us?
Stay low!
[foreboding music]
The magical storehouse
is just beyond these trees.
[footsteps approaching]
Wolf Mask Warriors.
Could they know
where we're headed?
[leaves rustling]
This is not how I expected
my day to go, which is weird.
I drink fortunetelling
tea every morning.
You'd think it'd
give me a heads up.
Jiro, stay hidden here.
We'll be right back.
[Jiro growls]
[ominous music]
Lord Ras, I--
I've managed to find the Ninja.
Not sure I can hold
the image for long.
The Blood Moon is here,
and the Ninja are too close.
You have to stop them.
Uh, from here?
That's impossible.
Can we send warriors?
Use the forbidden magic
you've been studying, Jordana.
But I'm a scientist.
I've only just started
learning the magic
on the scrolls
you've shown me, and--
I have no tie for failure!
[Jordana sighs]
The Ninja are far, but
[Jordana groaning]
As far as I know,
the Wyldness should
be the land up ahead.
-[thunder rumbling]
-[suspenseful music]
Look out!
Hold on!
Sora, watch out!
This wind is unnatural.
-Hold on!
-[all exclaiming]
-[Arin grunts]
-No!
[Lloyd screaming]
This looks bad, this looks bad,
this looks bad!
[everyone screaming]
Worse than I thought!
[foreboding music]
-Are you kidding me?
-[ship creaking]
[Sora and Kai gasping]
Whee!
Shh!
No sudden movements.
[both screaming]
[both grunt]
I can't believe it. We're safe.
[both screaming]
Okay, now we're sa--
-Now we're--
-[both screaming]
Now we're--
-[suspenseful music]
[Lloyd screaming]
You're flying!
[Riyu growls]
Or sort of flying.
[screams]
[Lloyd grunting]
We're alive. You saved me!
[Riyu growls]
-[mysterious music]
-[ship creaking]
Is everyone okay?
What's down there?
Oh, just nothingness.
Instant doom.
[foreboding music]
We need to get up to the top.
My Climber Mech!
Day saved! Boom!
[ship creaking]
Please don't say boom.
[chuckles] Oops!
[Sora] The Climber Mech
is a great idea,
but we can't get to it
without tipping the ship.
We'd for sure fall
into all that
Ugh!
[ominous music]
Nothingness and instant doom.
Yeah, that.
If we jump together in
exactly the right place,
I think we can tilt the ship
enough in the right direction
for Kai to get to the mech.
I'm ready to try it.
Okay, on the count of three,
we all jump,
land hard, the ship tilts up.
Then, Kai, you get to
the mech as fast as you can.
-Got it?
-Got it!
One.
Two.
-Three!
-[suspenseful music]
[Kai grunting]
Piece of cake!
-Faster!
-Almost [screams]
We're going over!
[both screaming]
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
-[computer beeps]
-Yes!
[both screaming]
-[rocks thuds]
-[Kai sighs]
-[rock thuds]
-[Kai yells]
[pensive music]
Sorry, Bounty.
You were a real good ship.
But onward--
And upward.
[Kai grunting]
[mysterious music]
This is the magical
storage house?
It's cute, but it doesn't
look big enough for all of us,
or even one of us.
-[whimsical music]
-You misunderstand magic.
-[door rattling]
-Gah!
Oh. It's stuck.
[sorceress grunting]
Ah!
Hold this.
Let me try an opening spell.
And
[crystal ball zaps]
Ouch! Oh, for crying
out loud in the morning!
-[footsteps approaching]
-Shh! Listen!
They're almost here!
[foreboding music]
This should do it.
[crystal ball zapping]
[mysterious music]
Ha! Take that, Janet!
Hurry! Let's go!
[ominous music]
[mysterious music]
Okay.
I do misunderstand magic.
We did not anticipate
the Wolf Mask Warriors
would be here.
We must hide Bonzle quickly,
before we are discovered.
[whimsical music]
What is this place?
Hmm, this storage house
is where we mystical folks
store most of our
valuable magical items.
But nothing is alphabetized.
This is highly inefficient.
We have a system!
Or we used to, probably.
Aha! There it is!
Home, sweet
protective container.
Is this bigger
on the inside, too?
Yes.
Yeah.
No. Sorry!
Help me get this out.
That looked expensive.
And cursed.
But we have more
pressing concerns here.
This is my second-most
powerful creation.
After you, of course, my dear.
You will be perfectly
safe in here.
Once I have sealed it, no
one will be able to open it.
Not even this Lord Ras
you keep telling me about.
Do I really have to?
Just until
the Blood Moon passes,
which hopefully
won't be much longer.
Ras's army is hunting for us.
I regret, we have no
other options, Bonzle.
You'll be fine, dear.
Okay.
Oh, this is actually kinda cozy.
I'm going to seal you in
now and start the spell.
You ready?
[sighs] As ready
as I'll ever be.
I do not believe in
wishing people good luck,
but I hope random
probability outcomes
align to your benefit.
[clears throat]
[speaking in foreign language]
[clears throat] Nope.
Can you not look
at me for a sec?
I get nervous under pressure.
[Zane whistling]
[speaking in foreign language]
Wow. She really knows
what she's doing.
[speaking in foreign language]
Whoa!
Wait, no.
What, no?
I'm not doing that.
-Then who is?
-I don't know!
What's happening?
Let me out, let me out!
Get her out of there!
I'm trying!
[Zane] Look!
The runes are appearing.
It is Theroxian,
the forbidden language.
Come on!
[grunts] What the
-[Bonzle yells]
-[Kai gasps]
Thank you, Ninja.
Who are you?
What have you done?
Never seen her
before in my life.
[yells] My name is Jordana!
Oh, you Ninja, especially
the one you call Sora,
are my sworn enemies.
Still not ringing a bell.
[yells]
I knew I could trap you
with my old Imperium tech,
but I wasn't sure how I'd
contain the spell here.
I never thought you'd put
her in a cage yourselves.
I might be just learning
Theroxian magic,
but corrupting your
poultry magic, sorceress,
has proven to be quite simple.
Lord Ras will be
very pleased with me.
And now we have
everything we need
to begin the ritual
of the Blood Moon.
[Bonzle yelling]
Bonzle!
You'll have plenty of time
to think about your failures
trapped in this stinky
old mushroom building.
It's a mystical storehouse!
Don't care.
We gotta get outta
here and save her!
-[force field thuds]
-[Kai yells]
-[suspenseful music]
-[both screaming]
[eerie music]
[Lloyd grunts]
Whoa. That storm
was so disorienting.
I have no idea where we are,
or where the others
could've landed.
Well, I'm thinking
we head toward that.
[gentle music]
[Riyu grunting]
No, I don't know if
any of the other Ninja
survived the fall, Riyu.
But even if we're
the only two Ninja left,
it's up to us to save the world.
[foreboding music]
[closing theme music playing]